=My Fairy Doctor= =Episode 18=
= My Fairy Doctor = = الحلقة 18 =
What did he pawn?
ماذا رهن؟
The jade pendant.
قلادة اليشم.
He wanted to show that
أراد أن يظهر ذلك
he had more money than Nianzhou.
كان لديه أموال أكثر من Nianzhou.
Are you out of your mind?
هل جننت؟
How could you pawn the jade pendant?
كيف يمكنك رهن قلادة اليشم؟
Qizi.
بنت.
Give me my share.
أعطني نصيبي.
(Hengchang Pawnshop)
(مرهن هنغتشانغ)
This jade pendant is very important to you.
قلادة اليشم هذه مهمة جدًا بالنسبة لك.
Don't do such a stupid thing again.
لا تفعل مثل هذا الشيء الغبي مرة أخرى.
I just want to make you happy.
اريد فقط ان اجعلك سعيدا.
I understand.
أفهم.
I'm happy.
أنا سعيد.
So
لذا
you're not angry anymore?
لم تعد غاضبا؟
I wasn't angry in the first place.
لم أكن غاضبًا في المقام الأول.
I see.
أرى.
You're very tolerant
أنت متسامح جدا
and never get angry,
ولا تغضب أبدًا ،
are you?
أنت؟
So annoying.
مزعج جدا.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
My name is Xixi.
اسمي Xixi.
Xixi.
يتبول.
Okay, this is yours.
حسنًا ، هذا لك.
Okay, thanks.
حسنا شكرا.
What about you?
وماذا عنك؟
My name is Zhuang Peiwen.
اسمي Zhuang Peiwen.
What's with
ما خطب
all these crowds?
كل هذه الحشود؟
No idea.
لا أعلم.
We've never had so many visitors before.
لم يكن لدينا الكثير من الزوار من قبل.
The handsome guy is here.
الرجل الوسيم هنا.
Hello, I am your fan.
مرحبا انا معجب بك.
Can you take a picture with me?
يمكنك التقاط صورة معي؟
Qizi.
بنت.
What's going on here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
The fans are so enthusiastic.
المشجعون متحمسون جدا.
They saw the shipping address
رأوا عنوان الشحن
and came to us.
وجاء إلينا.
(Mr. Handsome's Special Deals) One photo session with Mr. Handsome
(عروض السيد هاندسوم الخاصة) جلسة تصوير واحدة مع السيد هاندسم
with a purchase of RMB100 or more of herbs.
بشراء 100 يوان أو أكثر من الأعشاب.
Purchase over RMB500,
شراء أكثر من RMB500 ،
photos and handshake.
الصور والمصافحة.
Purchase over RMB1,000,
شراء أكثر من 1000 يوان صيني ،
photos, handshake and hug.
الصور والمصافحة والعناق.
Never pass up an opportunity to earn money.
لا تفوت فرصة لكسب المال.
I learn this from you.
أنا أتعلم هذا منك.
Why don't you do it yourself?
لماذا لا تفعل ذلك بنفسك؟
I'm not good-looking enough.
أنا لست حسن المظهر بما فيه الكفاية.
Modern people are open-minded.
الناس المعاصرون منفتحون.
You must dedicate yourself to the clinic.
يجب أن تكرس نفسك للعيادة.
Don't you get jealous
لا تغار
seeing him like that?
رؤيته هكذا؟
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
Why did you even kiss him?
لماذا حتى قبلته؟
Tang Caichen, come back and eat!
تانغ كايتشن ، عد وتناول الطعام!
Why?
لماذا ا؟
The fans are so excited now.
المشجعين متحمسون جدا الآن.
Are you dumb?
هل انت غبي؟
Think about it. If they ruined him,
فكر في الأمر.  إذا خربوه ،
who will go live with you?
من سيعيش معك
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Listen up.
اسمع.
That's all for today.
هذا كل شيء لهذا اليوم.
How am I doing today?
كيف حالك اليوم؟
I was holding back my discomfort.
كنت أحجم عن عدم ارتياحي.
I followed your instructions.
لقد اتبعت تعليماتك.
Money comes first.
المال يأتي أولا.
Didn't you like it?
ألم يعجبك؟
I saw how much you enjoyed it.
رأيت كم استمتعت به.
I did all that
لقد فعلت كل ذلك
for you and the clinic.
لك وللعيادة.
Well done then.
أحسنت صنعًا بعد ذلك.
Blackout again.
انقطاع التيار الكهربائي مرة أخرى.
I haven't washed up yet.
أنا لم أغتسل بعد.
It's uncomfortable to sleep like this.
من غير المريح أن تنام هكذا.
It's fine.
لا بأس.
I won't complain.
لن أشكو.
It's not the first day we've slept together.
إنه ليس اليوم الأول الذي نمنا فيه معًا.
All right.
حسنا.
But...
ولكن...
But what?
ولكن ماذا؟
Time is valuable.
الوقت ثمين.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Dabao.
داباو.
You...
أنت...
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
You
أنت
get up off me first.
استيقظ عني أولاً.
Tang Qizi.
تانغ كيزي.
Do you two think I don't exist?
هل تعتقدان أني غير موجود؟
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪ تضيء كل النجوم
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪ أتمنى البقاء معك إلى الأبد
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪ أنت مثل سلالة تانغ المزدهرة ♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪ لا يهم إذا كنا قدّرنا أم لا
♪We still love each other♪
♪ ما زلنا نحب بعضنا البعض